investorsinsight.com 2009-06-22

# InvestorsInsight's Privacy Policy - InvestorsInsight.com | Financial Intelligence, Advice & Research / Investment Strategies & Planning for Individual Investors.

InvestorsInsight Publishing, Inc. ("InvestorsInsight") recognizes that personal privacy is an important issue, so we design, maintain and operate our services with the protection of individual privacy as one of our utmost concerns. Our readership and subscriber databases are securely maintained for the proprietary publication and distribution of selected newsletters, financial and economic data and timely news reports and notices. 

In this recently revised and expanded Privacy Policy we set out examples of the types of information we collect and how we may possibly share that information and with whom. These examples are provided for illustration purposes and should not be considered a complete and exhaustive listing of our information collection, use and sharing practices. 

**Information Obtained.** When you register to receive any of our publications, we usually obtain, at the minimum, your name, your e-mail address and zip code. When you elect to "contact us," we may obtain additional information including your name, e-mail address, phone number, address and company name. We utilize this information to respond to individual inquiries as appropriate and to send you selected newsletters, financial data and timely news reports and notices. From time to time, we may forward additional information to you including special offers from InvestorsInsight or specially selected partners who offer products, services, or information which we believe may be of interest to our readership.  By providing your contact information and/or registering to receive any of our publications and/or viewing our web and e-mail information, you consent to the establishment of an "opt-in business relationship" between you and InvestorsInsight. 

InvestorsInsight also collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser customarily makes available whenever you visit any website on the Internet or open an e-mail.  This information may include your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your access and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information on an aggregate basis, to analyze the readership trends of our e-mails and access to our publishing services.

Some of our newsletters, reports and notices as well as our website may include ads from third parties. In order to measure advertising effectiveness, we may employ cookies or action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons). Any information that is collected via cookies and action tags is maintained under the same security measures as employed for personal information. 

**Third Party Information Gathering.** From time to time, ads or messages we send to you or that we post to our website may contain links that take you away from the InvestorsInsight message or web site, to third party landing pages or web sites that we do not control. We are not liable for any information you may choose to share with any third parties on their landing pages or web sites; we are not liable for and do not control how they might share the information that they collect from you.

**Information Sharing.** We are required by law to provide information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, from law enforcement agencies or state and federal regulators. If we sell or otherwise transfer substantially all of our assets related to this website, we will contractually require such third parties to honor our current Privacy Policy, until the third party provides you with notice of changes to the Privacy Policy and permits you to exercise any nondisclosure rights you may have under applicable law.

_We do not sell InvestorsInsight's subscribers' e-mail addresses to third parties._ We may, however, provide selected information that we have obtained on a confidential basis to certain nonaffiliated companies who are considered to be joint venture or strategic partners, advisors, contractors or consultants who are working with InvestorsInsight. Information will be shared with such third parties only to the extent reasonably necessary, and pursuant to confidentiality obligations. 

Non-personal information may be compiled for statistical purposes and provided to third parties. However, none of this non-personal data will include individually identifiable information. 

**Information Security.**   InvestorsInsight diligently works to insure the integrity and security of our network and systems. InvestorsInsight, however, cannot guarantee that our security measures will totally prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining access to such information.

**Updating Your Information.**   If you wish to update or change your information, you may go to our website and select "subscriber services." The screen that appears allows you to update or change your e-mail address.

**Opting Out.** We hope you value the unique and insightful publications and information we publish. You can, however, choose to opt-out of individual communications at any time by following the simple instructions provided in each e-mail.

**Changes to This Policy.** This Privacy Policy may be updated at any time, at InvestorsInsight's sole discretion. We expect that most changes will be minor. However, from time to time the changes can be significant. In either case, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice on our website home page. The date of the last revision to our Privacy Policy appears at the end of this notice.

If you have any questions regarding our website or this Privacy Policy, please e-mail [webmaster@investorsinsight.com](mailto:webmaster@investorsinsight.com). 

InvestorsInsight Publishing, Inc.  
06/18/08
